{
"data": [
    {
      "question": "a dish\n\n---> three ___",
      "answer": "dishes",
      "explain": "\n\n- The plural of nouns is usually formed by adding - s to a singular noun\n- Nouns ending in s, z, x, sh, and ch form the plural by adding - es\n\n- dish -> dishes\nRemember: Nouns ending in s, z, x, sh, and ch -> + es.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a friend \n\n---> nine ___ ",
      "answer": "friends",
      "explain": "\n\n- The plural of nouns is usually formed by adding - s to a singular noun\n- Nouns ending in s, z, x, sh, and ch form the plural by adding - es\n\n- friend -> friends",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a box \n\n---> seven ___ ",
      "answer": "boxes",
      "explain": "\n\n- The plural of nouns is usually formed by adding - s to a singular noun\n- Nouns ending in s, z, x, sh, and ch form the plural by adding - es\n\n\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a puppy \n\n---> three  ___ ",
      "answer": "puppies",
      "explain": "\n\n- Nouns ending in - y preceded by a consonant is formed into a plural by changing - y to - ies\n\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a rabbit \n\n---> eight ___ ",
      "answer": "rabbits",
      "explain": "\n\n- The plural of nouns is usually formed by adding - s to a singular noun\n- Nouns ending in s, z, x, sh, and ch form the plural by adding - es\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a baby\n\n---> seven ___",
      "answer": "babies",
      "explain": "\n\n- baby -> babies\nRemember: Nouns ending in - y preceded by a consonant -> changing - y to - ies.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a theory\n\n---> 11 ____",
      "answer": "theories",
      "explain": "\n\n- theory -> theories\nRemember: Nouns ending in - y preceded by a consonant -> changing - y to - ies.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a potato\n\n---> six ___",
      "answer": "potatoes",
      "explain": "\n\n- potato -> potatoes\nMost nouns ending in o preceded by a consonant -> +es.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a studio\n\n---> nine ___",
      "answer": "studios",
      "explain": "\n\n- studio -> studios\nMost nouns ending in o preceded by a vowel -> +s.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a self\n\n---> six ___",
      "answer": "selves",
      "explain": "\n\n- self -> selves\nSome nouns ending in f or fe -> changing f or fe to - ves. ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "4"
    }
  ]
}